DEFINITION:(TENEN BAUM):It is a Almost Complete Binary tree having heap propert
                        heap property can be of 2 types:
                        1.max heap property 2. min heap property.
Max Heap Property: Parent data is always greater or equal to children data.
MIN Heap Property: Parent data is always smaller or equal to children data.

Almost Complete Binary Tree :

Binomial_heap:Definition (wikipedia):
A binomial heap is implemented as a collection of binomial trees (compare with a binary heap,
 which has a shape of a single binary tree). A binomial tree is defined recursively:

    A binomial tree of order 0 is a single node
    A binomial tree of order k has a root node whose children are roots of binomial trees of 
    orders k−1, k−2, ..., 2, 1, 0 (in this order).


Fibonacci_Heap:(wikipedia)
   A Fibonacci heap is a collection of trees satisfying the minimum-heap property, that is, the key 
of a child is always greater than or equal to the key of the parent. 
This implies that the minimum key is always at the root of one of the trees. 
Compared with binomial heaps, the structure of a Fibonacci heap is more flexible. 
The trees do not have a prescribed shape and in the extreme case the heap can have every element 
in a separate tree. This flexibility allows some operations to be executed in a "lazy" manner, 
postponing the work for later operations. For example merging heaps is done simply by concatenating 
the two lists of trees, and operation decrease key sometimes cuts a node from its parent and forms 
a new tree.